Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
The Eye of the Midnight Sun set themselves up as the enemy of the Clover Kingdom and worked behind the scenes with the intent of establishing their own sovereign state.
They believed that gathering the items known as magic stones would allow them to be reborn in their true forms, granting them great power.
However, they must still collect three more before this rebirth can occur.
One of these stones was in the Underwater Temple, part of a strong magic region where the mana is said to be especially powerful.
Thank you, Yami. I'm counting on you. Oh, and Asta!
The Eye of the Midnight Sun
We'll be right back.
Are you listening?
Yes, sir.
Well, good.
A scream?
I think it came from down there.
It sounds like someone's in trouble.
Let's go!
Oh, just get it off already.
That voice!
A robbery?
Noelle!
What's going on?
You're the ones who came barging in here!
Swimsuits?
That's right.
Swimsuits, golden boy.
Excuse me.
We're taking a trip, heading to the beach.
Noelle here doesn't have a swimsuit, so I offered to help her pick one out.
Personally, I thought it would be easier if she just borrowed one of mine.
But she declined.
It was nothing but strings!
You expect me to wear that?
Oh my, that sounds interesting.
So then all the screaming we heard earlier...
That was when Vanessa started ripping my clothes off without permission!
I was helping.
It's not like you can try a swimsuit on over your clothing.
That's the kind of thing you have to be naked for.
Back me up!
Can we leave now?
Here, what do you think of this one?
Adding some little seashells doesn't make it any better!
Only a false alarm, then.
Trying on swimsuits for a beach trip?
Is that what constitutes hard work for the Black Bulls?
Excuse me, this is for a mission.
A mission?
That's right.
And it's one big secret job.
So, you want to come with, kiddo?
Adorable.
There are other things we need to be doing.
I'll have to pass.
That's a shame.
I'd love a trip to the beach.
Our next mission starts tomorrow, though, so we're all booked up.
Oh, that is a shame.
My Prince of Professions is here!
I wanted to see you in a swimsuit, too, Noelle.
My darling has never seen me in a swimsuit before!
I wonder what he'll say!
It's too much!
I can't handle the sexiness.
You're...
delicious.
You think so?
Keep me right up!
I'm ready!
Hey, wait!
Where did my sweet friend go?
You mean the golden boy?
He and his friends all left.
It looks like Charmy's got her suit picked out.
Now you just need to decide on one.
Here, how about this?
What?
Not a chance!
That doesn't cover anything!
Maybe you should consider that one over there.
Which one?
It is a bit pricey, of course.
I'm not worried about the cost.
And it has a certain charm, but...
I don't know.
There's still a lot of skin showing.
And does it really have to be that shiny?
Wear this to the beach, and you're sure to have all eyes on you.
All eyes?
What about Asta?
Will his eyes be on me, too?
This might actually get a compliment out of him.
Not that I care about getting a compliment from him, of all people.
So, um, is this the one you want, then?
I'll take it!
Let's go!
And keep the change!
What?
All right, gang!
We ready to roll out?
I'm so sorry, my dearest Marie.
I wish that I could take you along to get a glimpse of the beach.
I wonder which one's stronger, a whale or a shark?
A shark skin may look smooth, but it actually has a rough texture.
What the hell do you two think you're doing?
Don't just plop your butts on my crazy cyclone without asking!
Well, I can't really fly, so I kind of had to hitch a ride.
Same here.
Or did you forget?
What an idiot.
Oh yeah, Miss Priss?
If you're gonna be like that, then get a ride from somebody else!
A royal is deigning to ride with you.
You should be more grateful, commoner.
You're the one who can't fly!
Hey, Captain Yami isn't still sleeping, is he?
No, he said he was going ahead of us to check on something.
Wow, so miracles really do happen.
The captain is actually working?
Yep, that's our Yami for you!
All right, Black Bulls, the beach is waiting for us!
Crazy cyclone, move it out!
Yeah!
Asta and the other Black Bulls were headed for the seaside village of Rockway.
The strong mana in the area kept it warm year-round, making it a popular vacation destination for royalty, nobility, and magic knight squads alike.
Wouldn't it have been easier to use your spatial magic to get there, Finral?
This is my first visit to Rockway!
You should know by now, I can only use my magic to go to places I've been before!
What good are you?
Flying there like this is a complete waste of time!
I'm your superior, damn it!
There's a shock.
I figured you would have made it your life's mission to visit any place where you were guaranteed to find a bunch of babes in bikinis.
Huh.
I've always found half the pleasure of something lies in the anticipation of it.
I've long anticipated this.
Yes, Rockway, here I come!
It won't be long now, lovely ladies!
Wait, where's that person who's always blowing smoke and making that growling noise?
I'm right here!
Huh?
That was actually Grey transformed this whole time?
And if that's Grey, what happened to the real Gordon?
Hey, everyone.
Are you still asleep?
But, uh, shouldn't we be heading out?
Wait, did they...
Did they all leave without me?
Okay, we should be seeing it any second now.
Seeing what?
The ocean, little Rasta.
I can't wait.
I've never laid eyes on it.
Me neither!
We've been flying for a while now.
Do you think it'll be much longer?
I mean, I figured we would have seen it.
What are you talking about?
You're both staring right at it.
See all that blue?
No way!
This is it?
I never knew it was that big!
It's more incredible than I ever imagined.
It's the ocean!
Wow, we're really here!
The ocean!
And it's freaking enormous!
This is awesome!
So awesome!
I wish you and the kids back home could see this!
Um, hello!
And I've definitely got to bring Sister Lily here someday.
What am I, tub liver?!
Isn't the sunset beautiful, Rasta?
Indeed.
It certainly is.
But, Sister...
It's still not as beautiful as you.
I am the Wizard King now, so please, Sister Lily.
Mew?
Say that you'll marry me!
Of course!
I can just see it now!
Oh yeah, it's gonna be perfect!
What's that goofy look on his face for?
Wait, he's not thinking about that stupid kiss she gave him, is he?
Well, if he is, he should knock it off already.
Not that I care.
I don't want to kiss him or anything.
Maybe it's time to give that insect a proper eyeful of this new swimsuit.
He better not get the wrong idea, though.
I don't want him to want me.
I just want him to see that I'm more appealing than Rebecca.
Yeah, that's all.
No, too embarrassed.
But I want him to see me.
Ah, but I'm too embarrassed.
Just do it!
I got a new swimsuit!
Hey, Asta, what do you think?
Check it out!
The rest of you guys got nothing on there!
Is that your swimsuit, Magna?
Bold choice!
Sexy, huh?
Instead of going traditional, I figured I'd wear a loincloth like Yammy does.
How lame.
And now it's time to swim in the sea as big as our captain's heart!
You ready, Asta?
Ready!
Let's do it, Magna!
Hey, have you two seen my new suit?
What?
Well, what do you think?
Looks pretty good, right?
Actually, that's more or less what you always look like.
Mm-hmm.
What would a virgin street punk like you understand about it anyway?
I'm not a virgin street punk!
How about a race?
All right, Magna's on fire!
Will you stop running around like idiot children?
It's done.
Do you like your big brother's sculpture?
Yes, it's amazing!
Will you turn me around?
Show me the ocean!
Absolutely, Angel.
Well, there it is.
What do you think?
Oh, wow!
It's so beautiful!
Next time, I'll bring you two and we'll splash around in the water together.
Ooh, that's really cold.
Hey, Asta's there!
When you bring me to the beach, can he come along with us?
So, um, I got a new swimsuit, Asta!
Feel free to turn around and check it out if you want.
Anybody who would tempt Marie must die.
Hey, Asta!
Mirror magic, reflect Ray!
It's so salty!
Right, I can't sweat!
This isn't good!
Come on!
Will you look at me already?
Cash!
Oh, yeah!
So many bathing suit beauties to choose from!
So many!
It's time to get flirty!
All right, Gray, transform into me!
Let's go!
Now there's twice the finral to go around!
Okay, here's the plan!
We're sexy twins who use witty banter to lure the ladies in!
Think you can handle it?
Of course!
I'm you!
Visualize the watermelon!
You can do this!
No one knows food better than you!
Ah, wonderful!
There's something about the beach that just makes a drink taste better!
Move right, Charmy!
Just a little bit more and you should have it!
Oh, hey!
Aren't you supposed to be helping Finral with his flirting?
I was for a little while, but that got old so I decided to ditch him.
A couple steps to the left, Charmy!
No, you need to go right!
Left!
I've got it!
Almost there!
Just another ten steps!
I thought I was a goner!
Hey, uh, you know, this is new.
Gotcha!
You can't just go around hitting people with sticks, Charmy!
If that had been anyone else, they'd be dead now!
Oh, look, watermelon juice!
My head's not a watermelon!
Hello!
Don't forget my swimsuit!
Hey, look!
Transforming into you reminded me how gross being all buff like this is!
You really gotta find some serious uses for that transformation magic, Gray!
God!
You're wasting it!
What about my swimsuit?
Oh, hey!
Do you like it?
I knew it!
This sand is awesome for leg training!
Feel the burn, yeah!
You will look at me in my swimsuit, and you're going to do it right now!
Jeez, you still haven't learned how to control your magic yet?
I mean, not that I'm complaining.
Aw, you're planning to win out.
I don't have my wand right now, so local defensive spells are the only ones I can cast.
You're bragging about that?
Oh!
Oh, ha-ha!
Ah!
Oh!
Ha-ha!
So this is the famous Rockway Beach!
I can hear the ocean calling my name.
Is now really the time to be relaxing?
Yeah, don't you have work to do or something?
Well, I've just accomplished so much lately.
The Wizard King personally awarded me 100 stars!
Ha-ha!
Even Captain Jack himself praised my efforts.
Thanks to me, dozens of innocent children were rescued from an evil traitor's clutches!
What's the harm in taking a little break to stop and smell the roses?
Well, hello there, ladies!
Looking lovely today.
And where did you come from?
Home.
Home, huh?
Well, now that you're here, want to hang out?
Yeah, no thanks.
No, wait!
Hold on a second!
Please come back!
Some creeps prowling the beach for unsuspecting girls.
Why don't you guys pick up some ladies of your own?
What?
With you?
Ha-ha!
I could never do something as vulgar as that!
No, I'll simply meet back up with you once you've had some success.
Which basically means he's gonna wander over, crash our party, and act like he's the one
doing us a favor.
Remember, the only reason you're here is because you happen to have a friend among the Magic
Knights.
I've given you a killer opportunity.
Now, off you go!
So, we're doing this?
Do we have a choice?
What's that?
I see the perfect targets for you right over there!
Ha-ha!
Now don't worry about me, boys!
Go get them!
You go get them.
Hey.
Hey there, cuties!
Great day for a swim, isn't it?
Do you have a few minutes to chat with us about how awesome magical girls are?
Leave us alone, insects.
Wait!
That's the girl from the Black Bulls.
No way!
So he must be...
Huh?
Eat this!
Explosive!
Get a shot!
Reflect ray!
Ha!
Huh?
Oh, boy.
Any idea what I hit?
Nope!
It felt like I hit something, too!
Hey, gang!
We came here to look for the magic stone, didn't we?
So?
What are you messing around for?
Like you're not.
Oh, hi, Captain Yummy.
Okay, you incompetent knuckleheads, listen up.
While you were all busy goofing off, I was outscoring us some intel.
Huh?
Apparently, the underwater temple is beneath the surface of the ocean around here.
Unfortunately, the mana-driven currents are too strong, so even a skilled mage can't normally get near it.
The only time the mana is weak enough to even possibly access it is during a full moon.
What?
Captain Yummy's actually doing his job, and he's super serious about it?
Someday, I'm really gonna kill ya.
If you didn't guess already, the underwater temple is on the ocean floor.
You need magic to get there.
So, Noelle...
Huh?
That's where your water magic comes in.
We're gonna hitch a ride on it.
But, sir...
I'd need exceptional control over my magic to manage something like that.
No, I can't do it!
Find someone else!
If you were all relying on me and I messed up...
We die.
You blow this and that's it for us.
We get swallowed by the current and drown.
This is a top-secret mission the Wizard King entrusted to the Black Bulls alone.
There is no someone else.
It's just you, Noelle.
The full moon's a week away.
You've got till then to learn to control your magic.
Push past your limits.
See Dragon's Lair.
Currently my only spell.
Developing it should be the quickest way to get where I need to be.
Still.
Vanessa taught me some tricks to control my magic.
But no matter how many times I try, it never seems to go very well.
I just don't have the knack for it.
And maybe I never will.
But that's no excuse.
There's no reason to run away.
I'll just keep trying until I can do it.
I've got it!
So, you're out here training too?
You're training?
Please, I'm royalty.
We're just naturally perfect.
Hey, why don't we train together?
Hmm?
I can stop your spells if they go crazy.
No one will get hurt.
You're right.
As if I would make a mistake like that again.
Just the two of us training.
Well, fine.
If you insist, I suppose training with you wouldn't be the absolute worst.
Huh?
Hey, Astia?
I hear something.
Huh?
You're right.
Yeah.
And you're right.
New Looks
I wish you were here
Kimi ga kureta all those letters
Yumi kaisu tabi ni
The pain's gone
Hitoりじゃない
Could be a perfect transport
Hanaればなれでも
Tsureがる believe in you
いつも側に感じているから
Closer to me
And I'll go before you
Kimi ni call
You know you're not alone
Cuz we are perfect as born
Hanaればなれでも
Tsunagaru you live in me
いつも側に
Watashi ga iru kara
Closer to me
And I'll go before you
Kimi ni go
Glow Reckless
Look at me
Hey dorksta look at me
Notice anything?
Huh?
How do you like me in a swimsuit?
Well
Wow
It's so sparkly
Isn't it heavy?
Bet you could keep birds away with that
Hmm
Like this scarecrow we had back at the village
Hey
What are you looking at you creep?
You told me to love it
Well stop it
Stupid stuff
Haha
Did you enjoy another installment of Seke's stunning exploits?
I'm never more ha ha than when I ha ha at the shore
Black Clover page 41
The water girl grows up
One two three ha ha